# **DECLAN LYONS**

### **SUMMARY**

Full Stack Web Developer with a passion for building functional apps and creative problem solving. Strong attention to detail from 3 years experience working in warehousing and data management with an interest in cloud computing and 3D animations. Dedicated life-long learner, always eager to develop new skills.

# **EDUCATION**

**Lighthouse Labs** 

July 2021 - Oct. 2021

Diploma of Web Development

LinkedIn Learning

Oct. 2021 - Current

Certificate in MEAN Stack Web Development

### **EMPLOYMENT**

Silk Plant Warehouse, Warehousing & Restocking

Aug. 2018 - July 2020

Responsible for receiving stock, storing/organizing the warehouse and restocking the floors

Down the Beaten Path, Data Migration

Sept. 2020 - Nov. 2020

Responsible for migrating product data from Excel to TradeGecko database as they were rebranding to World Design Imports

World Design Imports, Shipping & Receiving / Product Deliveries

Nov. 2020 - Apr. 2021

Worked receiving shipments and occasionally making out of town deliveries when needed.

# **SKILLS**

LANGUAGES: JavaScript, HTML, CSS / SCSS, Ruby, C#, TypeScript

**FRONT-END WEB DEVELOPMENT:** Angular, Angular Material, React, EJS, JQuery, Bootstrap **BACK-END WEB DEVELOPMENT:** Express, Ruby on Rails, PostgresSQL, MongoDB, NodeJS

### **PROJECTS**

Bridge

Sept. 2021 - Sept. 2021

Bridge is a full stack shipping logistics utility application. It allows users with intensive shipping requirements keep all of their information in one place, track their shipping packages, and receive live updates to their computers or phones. It is a school final project I built with my peers. I was responsible for the packages interface and integrating the Twilio API.